Like You've Never Seen Him Before
This Is It is a music, documentary film directed by Kenny Ortega.
A compilation of interviews, rehearsals and backstage footage of Michael
Jackson as he prepared for his series of sold-out shows in London.
Self, played by Michael Jackson.
Self, played by Orianthi.
Self, played by Kenny Ortega.
Self, played by Dorian Holley.
Self, played by Patrick Woodroffe.
Self, played by Bashiri Johnson.
The year 2009 saw the release of many films.
Seven made the top 50 list of highest-grossing films.
Also in 2009, the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences announced that as of that year, their Best Picture
category would consist of ten nominees, rather than five (the first time since the 1943 awards).
The film explores themes of concert, pop star, pop
culture, backstage, dance music.